<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Music with Intentional Meaning]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Music with Intentional Meaning]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:41:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parce Domine, by Bob Metivier]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Parce Domine, by Bob Metivier</h1><p>Parce Domine by Bob Metivier, released 08 March 2012</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b8314589dcdd55eae2fc3eee80bf98c910fbcc3f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/track/parce-domine</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">66df49ac-07bd-4c01-861a-45ed245b4447</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Walk With Me, by Bob Metivier]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Walk With Me, by Bob Metivier</h1><p>Walk With Me by Bob Metivier, released 04 October 2001 Walk with me in the desert See my hands pierced through All is lost and is suffered And what remains is true We will dance in the cool desert air As darkness falls upon us here Walk with me in</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6621d8f3577a8da9b1ac40d9bb50fbc3c0d7ffd1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/track/walk-with-me</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0f32df72-6078-4385-9195-b760830e4273</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lord, Send Out Your Spirit, by Bob Metivier]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Lord, Send Out Your Spirit, by Bob Metivier</h1><p>Lord, Send Out Your Spirit by Bob Metivier, released 26 March 2015 Lord, Send Out Your Spirit You gather the rain In far reaches of the heavens You take wild rivers to tame As they wander through the mountains All the world and its seed Taste the waters You created</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b8314589dcdd55eae2fc3eee80bf98c910fbcc3f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/track/lord-send-out-your-spirit</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a1665088-5a7c-4209-b669-94b95b1b9916</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Lord, Send Out Your Spirit    You gather the rain  In far reaches of the heavens  You take wild rivers to tame  As they wander through the mountains   All the world and its seed  Taste the waters You created  And in Your Spirit they breathe  They bring forth Your celebration    Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth    On the wings of the wind  In the glancing tongues of fire  Each fearful heart You enflame  With your burning, unceasing desire   Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth    Send down, Send down Your Spirit on us  Send down, Send down Your Spirit on us    You call each one by their name  Your sons and Your daughters  We hear Your call to proclaim  Your mercy… and Your power    Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth   Rain down, rain down, rain down on us  Rain down, rain down Your Spirit on us  … and renew the face of the earth   © 2002, Robert G. Metivier</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/lord-send-out-your-spirit-you-gather-the-rain-in-far-re/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">06e1bc8d-6322-4801-a8a3-9b120908eb5d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>(Chorus)  Listen,listen  In your heart  Live the love  For love you have been called  Listen, my children  In your heart  Remember that I still love you so.   Long have you struggled  I see your losses and your gains  As life proves so often  To be such an uneven game  But in love's shadow  Is the message still to be found  For the lost and the fallen  Soon find holy ground   (Chorus)   The race is to the quick  The well-kept and the learned  Not to the broken,  surrendered and burned  Yet burning is cleansing  And the broken are healed.  And when you surrender  You find love revealed   (Chorus)   Bring me your passion  Your life as your gift  Not just praises on high  But love well lived  For I am one with you  My peace will not fade  Enter the quiet  Of love with me this day   (Chorus)   ... Remember that I still love you so...   Copyright © 2000, Robert G. Metivier</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/chorus-listenlisten-in-your-heart-live-the-love-for-l/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">987e13c4-9bf5-4431-ae64-82738fd89a6c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Lord, Send Out Your Spirit from Embraced By the Spirit by Bob Metivier     Share / Embed  Wishlist 00:00 / 04:49 Digital Track</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/lord-send-out-your-spirit-from-embraced-by-the-spirit-by-bo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b3074c72-5a94-46cd-a656-0d13fcc81925</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Listen In Your Heart from The Lord Takes Broken Pieces by Bob Metivier     Share / Embed  Wishlist 00:00 / 03:48 Digital Track  Includes unlimited streaming via the free Bandcamp app, plus high-quality download in MP3, FLAC and more.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/listen-in-your-heart-from-the-lord-takes-broken-pieces-by-bo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c6317bae-9c65-4430-bed6-f3e882dff6bf</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The old wooden fence  Beaten and torn through the years  By the wind and the sudden storms  -all that nature could conspire to bring.  Yet it somehow managed to hold firm  In its simple purpose  To keep the strangers out and the restless in.    Blistered by the scorching sun  And frozen with the winter sleet  Merciless in their approach  To them a barrier to break  In their unstoppable freedom  But the struggle has its toll  And its frame once strong has since grown old   The workmen said its time to take it down  And build a new one in its place  Its tired planks now broken and spent  Unfastened to the point of disgrace  The nails have left gaping the place  Where long they had held firm  The wounds now far beyond repair.   So the members carelessly taken down  And thrown upon a glowing heap  What once were sap-filled limbs  Its young wood firm and green  Now lies kindling dry for the burn  And to the earth from which it sprung  It now solemnly returns.   Old wooden fence it is no more  Nor any sort of wood at all  Simple offspring of the earth  Ashen dust its final call....  But also fire,- and heat and light  It takes its long-awaited flight  Set free from the nails, and the wind and the storm.   (reprise anthem)  And it is restored though vanquished in flame  Now born anew, an ennobled slave  Released to climb unbound through the clouds  A soul set free from the past and the stony ground   And it is reborn a child of the sky  No more to sustain the wound or the pain  Coursing the air, never meant to return  For now it has attained the end forever yearned.   Copyright © 2001, Robert Metivier</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/the-old-wooden-fence-beaten-and-torn-through-the-years-by/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">163328b5-3656-46fb-8c64-12adb145627d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Old Wooden Fence from The Lord Takes Broken Pieces by Bob Metivier </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/track/the-old-wooden-fence</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eb1b9f0d-9d71-4a75-9a4c-3a7f7b89b14f</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Walk with me in the desert  See my hands pierced through  All is lost and is suffered  And what remains is true   We will dance in the cool desert air  As darkness falls upon us here  Walk with me in the desert  (We'll talk along the way)   ----------------------------------------------   Come with me to the mountain  Take a breath and look down  See the road lies before us  Leading to promised ground   And we will dance in the clear mountain sky  Let our spirits learn to fly  Come with me to the mountain  And see the journey's end   -----------------------------------------------   Work with me in the vineyard  See the fruit rich and full  Bursting forth in its yearning   To be carried home  And we will dance to a new song  Joy will fill our hearts  For soon we will be home  At the table of our Love   -------------------------------------------------   [Instrumental verse]   We will dance in the cool desert air As darkness falls upon us here Walk with me in the desert (We'll talk along the way)   Dedicated to the March, 2001 mission at St. Francis of Assisi Catholic Church- Oklahoma City, OK conducted by Rev. Michael J. Boulette , entitled "The Journey Within ... The Experience of Lent."   Copyright © 2001, Robert G. Metivier credits from The Lord Takes Broken Pieces, released October 4, 2001</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/walk-with-me-in-the-desert-see-my-hands-pierced-through-al/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5e442461-9caa-4e6d-bebc-a007d8d60cdd</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>