<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Music with Intentional Meaning]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Music with Intentional Meaning]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 01:19:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Lord, Send Out Your Spirit    You gather the rain  In far reaches of the heavens  You take wild rivers to tame  As they wander through the mountains   All the world and its seed  Taste the waters You created  And in Your Spirit they breathe  They bring forth Your celebration    Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth    On the wings of the wind  In the glancing tongues of fire  Each fearful heart You enflame  With your burning, unceasing desire   Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth    Send down, Send down Your Spirit on us  Send down, Send down Your Spirit on us    You call each one by their name  Your sons and Your daughters  We hear Your call to proclaim  Your mercy… and Your power    Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth   Rain down, rain down, rain down on us  Rain down, rain down Your Spirit on us  … and renew the face of the earth   © 2002, Robert G. Metivier</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/lord-send-out-your-spirit-you-gather-the-rain-in-far-re/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2726d929-d929-4d95-9db2-582aa4fa49c2</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 01:19:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Listen In Your Heart, by Bob Metivier]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Listen In Your Heart, by Bob Metivier</h1><p>Listen In Your Heart by Bob Metivier, released 04 October 2001 (Chorus) Listen,listen In your heart Live the love For love you have been called Listen, my children In your heart Remember that I still love you so.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6621d8f3577a8da9b1ac40d9bb50fbc3c0d7ffd1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/track/listen-in-your-heart</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0cf8290d-7770-4c5f-a8a1-b58bba1b8072</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 01:19:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The old wooden fence  Beaten and torn through the years  By the wind and the sudden storms  -all that nature could conspire to bring.  Yet it somehow managed to hold firm  In its simple purpose  To keep the strangers out and the restless in.    Blistered by the scorching sun  And frozen with the winter sleet  Merciless in their approach  To them a barrier to break  In their unstoppable freedom  But the struggle has its toll  And its frame once strong has since grown old   The workmen said its time to take it down  And build a new one in its place  Its tired planks now broken and spent  Unfastened to the point of disgrace  The nails have left gaping the place  Where long they had held firm  The wounds now far beyond repair.   So the members carelessly taken down  And thrown upon a glowing heap  What once were sap-filled limbs  Its young wood firm and green  Now lies kindling dry for the burn  And to the earth from which it sprung  It now solemnly returns.   Old wooden fence it is no more  Nor any sort of wood at all  Simple offspring of the earth  Ashen dust its final call....  But also fire,- and heat and light  It takes its long-awaited flight  Set free from the nails, and the wind and the storm.   (reprise anthem)  And it is restored though vanquished in flame  Now born anew, an ennobled slave  Released to climb unbound through the clouds  A soul set free from the past and the stony ground   And it is reborn a child of the sky  No more to sustain the wound or the pain  Coursing the air, never meant to return  For now it has attained the end forever yearned.   Copyright © 2001, Robert Metivier</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/the-old-wooden-fence-beaten-and-torn-through-the-years-by/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">985f4fa2-37ca-4477-a337-9450da8a4eb5</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 01:00:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Old Wooden Fence, by Bob Metivier]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Old Wooden Fence, by Bob Metivier</h1><p>The Old Wooden Fence by Bob Metivier, released 04 October 2001 The old wooden fence Beaten and torn through the years By the wind and the sudden storms -all that nature could conspire to bring. Yet it somehow managed to hold firm In its simple purpose To keep the strangers out and the restless in.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6621d8f3577a8da9b1ac40d9bb50fbc3c0d7ffd1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/track/the-old-wooden-fence</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ce7e65af-d61c-43a8-8be0-dd2147804a04</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:55:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>