<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Music  That Matters]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Music  That Matters]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Old Wooden Fence from The Lord Takes Broken Pieces by Bob Metivier     Share / Embed  Wishlist 00:00 / 04:53 Digital Track  Includes unlimited streaming via the free Bandcamp app, plus high-quality download in MP3, FLAC and more.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/the-old-wooden-fence-from-the-lord-takes-broken-pieces-by-bo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eb1b9f0d-9d71-4a75-9a4c-3a7f7b89b14f</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Walk with me in the desert  See my hands pierced through  All is lost and is suffered  And what remains is true   We will dance in the cool desert air  As darkness falls upon us here  Walk with me in the desert  (We'll talk along the way)   ----------------------------------------------   Come with me to the mountain  Take a breath and look down  See the road lies before us  Leading to promised ground   And we will dance in the clear mountain sky  Let our spirits learn to fly  Come with me to the mountain  And see the journey's end   -----------------------------------------------   Work with me in the vineyard  See the fruit rich and full  Bursting forth in its yearning   To be carried home  And we will dance to a new song  Joy will fill our hearts  For soon we will be home  At the table of our Love   -------------------------------------------------   [Instrumental verse]   We will dance in the cool desert air As darkness falls upon us here Walk with me in the desert (We'll talk along the way)   Dedicated to the March, 2001 mission at St. Francis of Assisi Catholic Church- Oklahoma City, OK conducted by Rev. Michael J. Boulette , entitled "The Journey Within ... The Experience of Lent."   Copyright © 2001, Robert G. Metivier credits from The Lord Takes Broken Pieces, released October 4, 2001</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/walk-with-me-in-the-desert-see-my-hands-pierced-through-al/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5e442461-9caa-4e6d-bebc-a007d8d60cdd</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Walk With Me from The Lord Takes Broken Pieces by Bob Metivier     Share / Embed  Wishlist 00:00 / 02:51 Digital Track  Includes unlimited streaming via the free Bandcamp app, plus high-</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/walk-with-me-from-the-lord-takes-broken-pieces-by-bob-metivi/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a1f0eee3-a671-41f0-b834-352784ca50ce</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>