<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Music with Intentional Meaning]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Music with Intentional Meaning]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 01:33:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/music-that-matters/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lord, Send Out Your Spirit from Embraced By the Spirit]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Lord, Send Out Your Spirit from Embraced By the Spirit</h1><p>Lord, Send Out Your Spirit from Embraced By the Spirit by Bob Metivier     Share / Embed  Wishlist 00:00 / 04:49 Digital Track  Immediate download of Lord, Send Out Your Spirit in your choice of 320k mp3, FLAC, or just about any other format you could possibly desire. You can support me directly without "feeding" Apple along the way with this one! Buy Now  $1 USD  or more Send as Gift  Buy the Full Digital Album about This is a celebration of Pentecost lyrics Lord, Send Out Your Spirit    You gather the rain  In far reaches of the heavens  You take wild rivers to tame  As they wander through the mountains   All the world and its seed  Taste the waters You created  And in Your Spirit they breathe  They bring forth Your celebration    Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth    On the wings of the wind  In the glancing tongues of fire  Each fearful heart You enflame  With your burning, unceasing desire   Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth    Send down, Send down Your Spirit on us  Send down, Send down Your Spirit on us    You call each one by their name  Your sons and Your daughters  We hear Your call to proclaim  Your mercy… and Your power    Refrain: Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth  Lord, send out Your Spirit and renew the  face of the earth   Rain down, rain down, rain down on us  Rain down, rain down Your Spirit on us  … and renew the face of the earth   © 2002, Robert G. Metivier credits from Embraced By the Spirit, track released March 26, 2015</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/track/lord-send-out-your-spirit</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0b558fb4-a02a-4b74-973b-34df2329f4a9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 01:33:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://f1.bcbits.com/img/a2345009720_16.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://bobmetivier.bandcamp.com/album/embraced-by-the-spirit</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b9e5ee43-ce54-4aa5-819d-2651caeb8371</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 01:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>